Ken ...
please ...
Stop !
Ken ?
Ken !
It 's me !
I 'm begging you !
Wake up !
I love you .
Okay , cut .
What do you think ?
How many takes ?
That was the 42nd .
You 're facing death .
Yes .
Were you really scared ?
Yes , as if it was ...
- for real . - You were acting , yeah ?
Yes .
Not as if , it should
come naturally !
Um , what do you mean ...
- come naturally ? - Give me real fear !
The true shiver in your face ! Face ! Face !
Wanna know why you look so fake ?
Coz your life itself is utter fake .
You say nothing but lies !
Why don 't ya peel off that lie-infested mask of yours ?
You 're over the line !
Shut up you idiot !
- This is my show , my work ! - Hey , come on .
You 've been talking back since rehearsal !
Listen ! Why don 't we take a breather ? Let 's take a break !
Can we take thirty , Director ?
He 's worse than usual today .
- I 'm gonna get some fresh air . - Yeah , okay .
- Are you okay ? - Yes , I 'm fine .
Talk to her .
How 're you doing ?
What 's with him ? He 's insane .
- No , it 's me , I 'm a lousy actor . - Nah .
There 's no point repeating that scene .
Bear with me .
You know , when you attack me ...
Do it harder .
Can I come tonight ?
I 'm dying for a hot bath ! Let 's have it together .
- Here you go . - Thank you .
Have a seat .
Jesus !
Whopping 42 takes , huh ?
I 'm so sorry .
Oh , no . Not you , he 's insane ,
You know this is a real axe ? So damn dangerous .
What now ?
The Director wants all the fake blood on the rooftop .
To the rooftop ? What for ?
Who knows ? Pour it all over himself to keep him going ?
What ?
The director is so wound up .
Especially this time .
He 's so committed to this film .
- And got into debt as well . - What ! In debt ?
- I 'm gonna practice by myself . - There 's no need . Don 't worry .
Come on , relax .
Sit down .
You 're working hard .
Who found this location anyway ?
Perfect for a horror film .
The director travelled all over Japan to find it .
This place 's like a real haunted house .
Funny you should say that .
What ?
It 's just an urban legend , like those you find on the net .
On the record ,
this place was built for water filtration .
But the Japanese army used here for some sort of experimentation .
- Experimentation ? - Human experimentation .
- What do you mean ? - Like ... bringing the dead back to life .
You mean ... ?
- Uncanny , huh ? - What ?
- Well , the story doesn 't end there . - What ?
Wow , what was that ?
What timing ! The wind ?
- Nao , do you have ... any ... - Huh ?
- Hobbies ? - Hobbies ?
That 's a random question .
Let 's have some fun here .
Not really a hobby but I 'm learning self-defense .
- Self-defense ? - Yep .
You see ,
I work with a lot of youngsters like you guys .
I teach them sometimes .
- I see . - I see .
Show me , what if you get ...
- attacked like this ? - From the front ?
- There ... - Ouch ! Aw !
- You go ! - Wow !
How about ... from behind ?
Oh . Okay grab me from behind then .
Okay , excuse me then .
Grab !
Pom !
- Wow ! You 're out ! - Amazing !
- Did you say pom ? - Saying it makes all the difference !
- You slipped out so easily . - Amazing !
Holy cow ! You made me jump .
They painted you , huh ?
You can be an actor .
Wanna play a part ? I 'll film it .
Hey , what 's wrong ? Hey !
Uh ?
Um ...
Seen this prop before ?
Oh my god .
This looks so real !
Disgusting ...
Wow , who made you a zombie ? The director ?
What ... ? He 's dead .
I get it ! That one is his arm ...
Not bad .
Wait a minute , this is some sort of prank , isn 't it ?
Come on , the show is over . You can get your arm out now .
He 's got no arm ! No arm !
He 's dead ! He 's really dead !
What 's this ? Gross !
Hey ...
can it be ... ?
No way .
It can 't be !
I don 't believe it !
This can 't be happening !
Director ?
What 're you doing ?
Shooting , obviously .
Don 't you know what 's happening ?
Hey !
- This is filmmaking ! - You 're insane !
- True filmmaking ! - No !
Look ! There 's no fiction , no lies . This is reality !
We keep rolling !
Don 't stop shooting !
- You didn 't , did you ? - What ?
Oh yes , a great guess !
I threw the blood already .
Blood ?
Impossible .
That was just an urban legend !
Hey ! What 're you talking about ?
It was ... around this time last year .
It was a goddamn hot summer !
I was writing the script of this film day and night .
One day , a rumor spread on the net ... Oi , where 're you going ?
- I just ... - You just ?
- Wait a second , just what ? - Just ...
- Huh ? - I 'll be right back .
There are monsters out there !
Yeah , I think It 's dangerous to go out !
But , I 'm just ...
What 's your problem , eh ? Just what then ?
- Just means ... just ! - Yamagoe !
Oh shit , no , no !
Let go ! Get off !
Get off !
Keep on shooting ! Keep it rolling !
Wait !
You hurt ?
I 'm all right .
- Are you all right ? - Yep .
I 'm fine , are you all right ?
I 'm all right .
You hurt ?
Oh , no ... he just asked ...
Oh ... yeah .
Um ... you ...
- Yes . I 'm okay . - That 's ... yeah .
We know that no one was hurt , that 's great !
No one injured which is amazing !
We 're all okay that 's just great !
Right ?
It 's no use . No signal around here .
Nao .
What the director said earlier .
Is that the same rumor ?
To revive the thing , chant a spell of blood .
- Huh ? - The rumor ...
The thing ?
I 'll explain later .
Let 's get outta here !
- What ? - By the car .
- What about the monsters ? - You got a better idea ?
No one will come to our rescue here !
What 's the thing ?
What the hell is going on in this place ?
Wha , what the hell ...
is ... go , going on in this place ?
Oi ... it 's me ! Open the door !
Wait !
I 'm alone ! There 's no monsters !
After three , okay ?
One , two ...
Action !
Wha ... h , holy crap !
This is what I wanted !
Yeah !
Yes , yes ! This is great ! Yeah !
This is damn good !
- Push the monster this way ! - So damn real !
What the hell ! This is fun-freakin ' - tastic !
Serves you right ! Freakin ' monster . Damn you !
Oh , yeah . That 's the face ! Nailed it !
This 'll be a goddamn sick film ...
Run to the car . I 'm gonna freakin ' smash them all !
Clear ! Keep running !
- There 's no key ! - What ?
- Who 's got it ? - Kasahara ?
Kasahara ! Damn !
Kasahara !
Kasahara ...
Action !
The bag ! The key might be in that bag !
C 'mon monster ! Get her !
- Chinatsu ! - Get off !
Get the hell out ! The camera is rolling !
Kg !
Nae !
Noooo !
Chinatsu !
Twisted my ankle .
- Where 's Nao ? - OK , she 's inside .
Nao ! It 's me , open the door !
- Nao ! Open the door ! - Please Nao !
Quick !
- Got the key . - Wait .
You got bitten ?
I 'm not sure .
It could be ... just a cut .
Nao ...
It 's okay , I know . Just in case .
- Calm down , Nao . - I 'm calm . I 'm dead calm .
No !
Pom !
Help !
Action !
Outta my way !
Stop it !
No ! No !
I gotcha !
Stop !
It 's okay , just a precaution .
- No ! - It 's okay .
- Nao ! - Who the hell are ya ?
Aw , aw , aw , it hurts !
Aw ! You 're gonna break my arm !
I 'm serious ! Stop her ! Stop the camera !
Don 't come near me !
- Go away ! - What ?
Run away from me !
Chinatsu !
An axe ...
Lucky me .
Kg !
Ko ?
Oh , no ...
You as well ?
What 's that ?
Ko ...
please ...
Stop !
That 's it !
That face ! You nailed it , goddamnit !
Now ... the climax ! Make it the last bloody take !
Ko ...
please ...
Stop !
Ko ?
Please Ko ! It 's me !
I 'm begging you !
Wake up !
Ko ?
Ko ...
please ...
Stop !
Please !
I love you .
Oi !
What the hell ? Follow the script !
Hey ! Jeez ... come on , stop it !
Okay , cut !
One month ago ..
Egreh ...
Milyfhghatddah !
Yep , okay !
- Okay . - Was it okay ?
- Yes , great face . - What about my lines ?
We don 't use them , just the image .
Oh , I got you .
Next in order , the tears .
Look up please .
What scene is it ?
Why am I crying again ?
- Rolling ! - Eye drops , okay !
Ready ? Action !
Oh , long time no see .
- Can we talk later ? - Yes .
- Mr. Higurashi , was that okay ? - Yep , okay .
- Mr. Higurashi , - Yes .
What 's your genre then ?
I do reconstruction VTRs a lot .
And karaoke videos , I do many little things .
What was it again , your pet phrase ?
It goes ... I 'm ...
Fast , cheap but average .
- That 's it ! - Sorry .
Sounds good .
I 'd say yes .
Really ?
Zombie film ?
We 're starting the Zombie Channel from this August ,
and making a special drama .
Can you elaborate on that ?
Whilst shooting of an indie zombie film ,
real zombies attack the crew .
They panic ! panic ! and fight ! fight ! against zombies .
A survival story .
I see .
And , there are two hot features !
Hot features ?
One , live broadcasting .
Real time ?
It 'll go on the air at I pm for 30 minutes .
- Two , the hotter feature , which is ... - Yes ?
One take .
One take ? You mean ...
With one camera .
One take , no cuts . With one camera from start to finish .
Making a zombie film
on a live broadcast ,
in one take ?
It 's hot , huh ?
Oh dear , oh my ...
What an absurd idea , that 's funny .
- Huh ? - What ?
We 're not kidding .
Dead serious .
What ?
What do you think ?
Pom !
Self-defense techniques for women No . 42 Pom Slide
Raise your arms up to the sky , '
bend your knees with a straight back .
And now , you say ...
- Pom ! - Out loud . This is the key .
The attacker flinches by pom , '
body down and slip through .
Pom !
Why did they come to you ?
No one took the offer , as it 's utter nonsense .
So did you , right ?
Eh ? Yeah ...
I knew it . You don 't have the guts to say no .
I 'll be home late .
- How about dinner ? - No .
Hey , Mao ...
- I 'm off ! - See you later .
What 's the new crew like ?
Are you off today ?
- Yeah . - Can you spy on her ?
What ?
I want the real ones . Your real tears .
Yeah ? You shouldn 't rely on a fake thing like this .
Ever cried from anger ? I have .
It was the last basketball match at my school ...
Hello , the director said it 's okay to use eye drops here .
Excuse me , but this is a battlefield .
Battlefield ?
She 's fighting her own battle .
No place for a mother to cut in .
- But I was told ... - Leave it Mao .
- Okay let 's go . - Director ,
- this is important . - There 's no time !
You shouldn 't listen to that old hag !
Old hag ? Me ?
Sorry about that but you must unders ...
No way , we 're leaving .
Wait Madam , please ! We must wrap it today ...
So sorry about the old hag .
Can we get back once , please ? So sorry ...
In terms of work she 's great ,
the problem is her personality .
- She doesn 't fit in our team . - Yes , I understand .
- Okay then . - I 'm sorry .
You know ... l think ...
you should learn to compromise .
As you 're leaving home soon , you must make a living .
I know you care so much about the details ...
Hey , Mao !
Taizo cried out loud on the roof top of the hospital .
It was the first tears he shed in his life .
Eye drops , huh ?
Taizo Kusokabe , a lonely entrepreneur ...
Can I change it ?
Of course you can .
Would you tell your opinion to the director while shooting ?
Well ...
Actor Kazuaki Kamiya I would if necessary for the sake of art .
- You 're recording this , right , Mom ? - Yes .
Who 's he ?
Her current favorite .
Any genre you want to challenge for ?
My next role is a challenge .
I can 't reveal too much yet ...
Fan I say it ? I can ?
I 'll be blood soaked .
Blood-soaked ? A horror movie ?
Casting candidates Actor Kazuaki Kamiya
just wait and see !
Thank you .
First reading room '
I was always interested in zombie films .
I 'm your big fan , I always wanted to work with you .
Actress : Miss . Aika Matsumoto I 'm your b I gfan , I a I w ays wanted t owork with you .
I 'm flattered !
Hey , would you mind doing ... ?
Sure . Aika 's love beam !
Actor : Mr. Kazuaki Kamiya Love it !
This story deals with the topic of racism discreetly .
- Yeah , maybe . - I noticed .
Mr. Manubu Hosoda '
To stop my hands shaking .
Oh , I see .
Mr. Hiroshi Yamanouchi '
- Uh , which part deals with racism ? - Sorry , I 'm in my zone right now .
Okay . I 'm sorry .
Excuse me .
Is this hard water ?
Sound : Mr. Shunsuke Yamagoe Pardon ?
I can only drink soft water .
Or I get bad diarrhea .
I 've emailed you .
- Oh ... I 'm sorry . - I 've emailed .
Give me real fear .
The true shiver in your face ! Face ! Face !
Director : Daigo Kurooka
I 'm sorry I 'm late !
- Nice to meet you . - Oh , hi !
What ?
I 'm sorry my husband is away and my manager is busy today .
Make-Up : Mrs. Mai Aida I 'm sorry my husband is away and my manager is busy today .
Shall I ?
It 's fine , she 's so quiet .
- This way . - Yes .
Director : Takayuki Higurashi
You 're facing death .
Yes .
Were you really scared ?
Yes as if it was for real .
You were acting , yeah ?
Yes .
Not as if , it should come naturally .
Um , what do you mean come naturally ?
The true shiver in your face ! Face ! Face !
You 're over the ...
You 're over the line !
Why don 't we take a breather ?
Take a break ?
Okay , let 's stop right here !
And ... this won 't be good either .
Covered in vomit ?
I 'd like to challenge myself but , my agency won 't let me .
Vomit on a pop star ? No !
Obviously it won 't be real vomit .
- Yes I know . - Okay ,
No vomit .
I 'm sorry , I don 't mind doing it but my agency does ...
I understand .
That 's great !
Okay .
- May I ? - Yes .
The AD zombie axes the Make-Up , right ?
- Yes . - Can a zombie use an axe ?
Um ... pardon ?
Zombies have no will , using an axe means he has will , yes ?
Well , zombies have many types ,
- so it can be possible ... - Am I talking to you ?
Okay - .
- Let me think about it . - Yes , please .
What 's the matter ? Say peek-a-boo !
And they 're having chat drinking coffee .
Then the first zombie , the AD zombie comes in .
You can fling yourself in , then those three guys get panicked .
Next , comes the DOP zombie , Mr. Hosoda .
Again , you just go for it . Make them feel twice as panicky as before .
- Taniguchi ! - Yeah ?
When the zombies appear , wouldn 't it be great if
you vigorously zoom in and out like this ?
What a cheesy idea .
As it 's cheesy it 'll look cool ! Whoosh ! Whoosh !
I don 't get it .
I won 't do it .
Are you okay ?
One take using a hand-held will kill me .
I 'm good with hand-held !
I 've already told you ,
you 're not ready for this .
- I 've studied the script inside out ! - No .
We practiced the Pom Sliding before .
Here , you 'll learn a variation of it .
- Hey , Mom . - Yeah ?
- Won 't you start again ? - What ?
- Acting . - Huh ?
I 'm leaving home soon ,
- do something you like . - You gotta be joking .
You love reading his scripts .
While killing time .
Killing time , huh ?
Pom and what !
- What 's this for ? - Huh ?
Defending what from who ?
Another time killer . A hobby .
Self-defense isn 't a hobby .
To be honest , I 'm running out of hobbies .
You get bored too easily .
You did yoga , ballroom dancing , and Hawaiian dancing .
- Then self-defense ? - Well , I 'm in a process of
discovering something that I can devote myself to .
Isn 't that acting ?
Oh , that ...
I devote myself too much .
Many good actors are like you , it 's not a bad thing .
- You should try again ... - You don 't know what you 're saying .
- Don 't you wanna try again ? - Forget about it , okay ?
He 's gonna direct a drama .
Oh , really ?
- A rare occasion . - I know .
Guess what ? Kazuaki Kamiya ...
He 's in it .
What ?
Nao , calm down .
I 'm calm .
- I 'm dead calm . - Nao !
AD zombie , from behind !
Snatch the axe , slam it down ,
and stuck on her head . Okay cut !
Still not convinced ?
Some zombies fire guns these days .
- You think too much . - Let me think .
Exactly .
This is one of my few good scenes in the film though .
I 'll convince him .
Please do .
- Hey . - Yes ?
- The first crying scene ... - Yes .
Can I use eye drops ?
Can 't you cry for real ?
Well , I think I can , but it 's more assuring , right ?
We can 't retake so better that way .
- Okay then . - That 's great !
Are there toilets in the building ?
We 're going to rent some portaloos .
I need to know how many and where , asap .
I understand .
I emailed as well .
Oh , I 'm sorry .
I emailed .
I 'm sorry .
Did you know ?
- I 'm sorry . - I said , did you know ?
Hey , crouch down a bit , will you ?
Oh yeah , stay down .
That 's good . Uh-huh .
Many strong characters , huh ?
You can talk , Hosoda !
Sorry about what I did .
I 'm not drinking .
Really ?
Until the shooting is done .
Are you sure ?
It 's a disgusting habit .
- Who 's this ? - My daughter .
My will-power charm , when my hands shakes .
My bad habit
is causing me to lose my daughter .
What ?
Last year ,
she agreed to meet me one day .
I got really nervous on the clay , started gulping down .
- Oh , no ! - I passed out ,
- so I didn 't make it . - That 's ridiculous !
Ridiculous indeed ! That 's my life .
Fun , though .
I wanted to make her proud of me .
It 's not easy .
I agree .
Hey , Hosoda ...
No need to cry about it .
Is it that hard ?
What 's up ?
Can I ask you a favor ?
What is it ?
Well ...
- Morning . - Good morning !
- Great location ! - Right ?
Hot water , please ?
- Gonna start . - Yep .
- Going up ! - Yep .
How 's does it look ?
Not bad . It 'll work .
- Keep hold of it ! - Okay .
We push in from the distance like this .
- Tilting a bit ? - Yes .
Sorry for the intrusion .
Oh no , she wanted to see his work ?
That 's right .
I heard you want to be a director ?
Yes , she does .
Like father , like daughter .
Children grow up watching their parents .
Get out of the way !
Yes , indeed .
Don 't worry about minor mistakes , keep going .
The camera won 't stop till the end .
Unless something goes wrong .
So please be careful , watch what you 're doing .
Look , from the handsome producer .
- Thank you . - Where from ?
Good sake from Niigata .
- Let 's drink later . - Later .
Hide it for now .
Yomagoe 's bottle '
Hey , have Kurooka and Soda arrived ?
- Stuck in the traffic . - No calls ?
- Won 't be long . - Call them again .
Higurashi .
- An accident ? - Yes .
Anyone hurt ?
Not badly , it was a minor collision .
They came in the same car ?
Isn 't that obvious ?
- Having an affair ? - Yeah !
- Go and check the rest . - Okay .
How 's it going ?
We have to cancel them .
- Is the show cancelled ? - No way .
- Work something out . - How ?
What 's the time ?
I I am , two hours to go .
Can 't you rewrite ?
It 's one take , no cuts ! Not a chance .
Then we find substitutes .
It takes 2 hours to get here .
- No one will make it in time . - Anyway ,
we can 't cancel the show .
Higurashi ?
Are you serious ?
I did some acting in high-school .
- Just a sec , wait ! - Who else is there ?
Who 'd fit the age , gender , and knows the script other than me ?
Yes .
- I agree . - But ...
Hold on ! Who will play the make-up artist then ?
Huh ?
She used to be an actor .
- Hey ... - Also ,
she secretly reads his scripts .
Do you know the lines ?
- Almost . I 've read it over 100 times . - What ?
But I can 't ...
You 've got the role .
Excuse me .
- Definitely not ! - Why ?
You 've no idea what Mom was like ! I suffered so much from it !
I shouldn 't do it .
Who else is there ?
Not Mom , definitely not !
No , I shouldn 't do it .
No way . I really shouldn 't do it .
Please to meet you !
It should be cancelled . For the sake of art ...
It 's ... a TV show before it 's art .
The viewers are waiting for us .
We must broadcast the show .
- So please ! - Even the TV show , my ...
You already know this but let me tell you , this is your show .
You are the star here .
It 's gonna be great .
I promise .
What 's wrong ?
I 'm just ...
I 'll be right back .
- Are you okay ? - Not a chance .
I 'm sorry .
I 'm fine , it 's funny a director playing a director .
Oh , don 't go easy on me , you are too kind .
- Okay then . - That 's great !
Listen everyone ,
we are about to start .
Just to clarify , it 'll be one long take , one camera .
Broadcasting live .
Once the camera starts rolling we can 't turn back .
Let 's make it work !
Count down from 10 seconds , nine , eight , seven ...
six , five , four , three , two ...
All right , here we go ! I 'm counting on you !
Ken , please ...
Wake up !
I love you ..
Cut .
What do you think ?
How many takes ?
That was the 42nd .
You 're facing death .
Yes .
Were you really scared ?
Nice one Director , he can act .
Not as if , it should
come naturally .
Um , what do you mean ...
Give me real fear !
The true shiver in your face ! Face ! Face !
Wanna know why you look so fake ?
Coz your life itself is utter fake .
You say nothing but lies !
Why don 't yo pee ! that hex-infested mask of yours ?
- He 's improvising . - What ?
Shut up you idiot !
This is my film , my work !
You 've talked back since rehearsal !
Why don 't we take a breather ?
- Great expression . - I know ,
she acts from her heart .
- Stay away . - Director .
I 'm sorry , I went full throttle .
Sorry . Stay out of their way !
Hosoda 's not here .
One minute to his cue .
What the hell ... what 's going on ?
Hosoda !
Hosoda , Hosoda !
Stinks of booze .
Get some placards .
I can 't believe it !
Uncanny , huh ?
- Well , the story doesn 't end there . - What ?
Here 's a problem , keep improvising !
Wow ! What was that ?
What timing . The wind ?
Nao , do you have any ...
- hobbies ? - Hobbies ?
- Hobbies . - That 's a random question .
Let 's have some fun here .
Not really a hobby but I 'm learning self-defense .
- Self-defense ? - Yep .
Pom !
- Wow ! You 're out ! - Amazing !
Are they crazy or what ?
- You slipped out so easily . - Amazing !
Director , what 's next ?
Holy cow !
You made me jump . They painted you , huh ?
You can be an actor . Wanna play a part ?
I 'll film it .
Hey , what 's wrong ?
Hey !
What was that liquid ?
Can you wipe my face ?
- No wipes ? - No .
What 's this ? Gross !
So realistic .
That is the key here .
Hosoda !
- Is it starting ? - It 's started !
Your cue , Higurashi !
Where 're you going ? Your cue 's next !
It was around this time last year . It was a goddamn hot summer !
I was writing the script of this film day and night .
One day , a rumor spread on the net ... Oi , where 're you going ?
- I just ... - You just ?
- Wait a second , just what ? - just ...
Where are we at ?
Nowhere . What the ...
There are monsters out there !
Yeah , I think it 's dangerous to go out !
- They 're improvising . - For real ?
What 's your problem ...
Oh , crap .
Yamagoe !
- The name . - Stop him !
Oh , crap , no , no !
Another one gone . I 'm getting excited !
- You got the card ready ? - Yes !
Please wait a moment ..
Keep on rolling ! Don 't stop shooting !
Where 's he looking ?
What 's wrong with you , Yamagoe ?
It 's coming out !
What is it ?
Poop ...
That 'll be a blooper .
- Are you all right ? - Yep .
I 'm fine , are you all right ?
They 're going on and on ...
Can 't you continue ?
Not without Yamagoe !
Let 's put the card up .
Bring Yamagoe back as a zombie , back to page I7 !
Woman ! Look !
From page 15 , row 15 here , to page 16 , row 11 ,
jump to this line , hurry up , Woman !
- Where ? - We good ?
- Row 11 , here . Here , idiot ! - Kind of .
Old man ! Decision , now !
- Um ... let 's do it . - Woman , placard !
We 're all okay , that 's just great !
Fiddle with a cell , jump to ' what 's going on ? '
Bring Yamagoe back as zombie !
It 's no use . No signal around here .
Sorry , toilet 's too far away .
It 's okay ...
- Do it now , no time to wait ! - What ?
Stop crying ! Hurry up !
Yes .
Oi , where 's Yamagoe 's head ? Head anyone ?
- Woman ! - Found it ? Okay , throw !
Have you seen Hosoda ?
- Grandpa ! - Starting ?
Get the hell up ! You ! Take over here .
Let 's nail the rest of it !
Who 's that ?
Action !
This is what I wanted ! Hell yeah !
Push the monster this way !
This is fun-freakin ' - tastic !
Serves you right ! Freakin ' monster . Damn you !
Oh , yeah . That 's the face ! Nailed it !
This 'll be a goddamn sick film ...
Run to the car . I 'm gonna freakin ' smash them all !
This way !
- There 's no key ! - Who 's got it ?
- Kasahara ? - Kasahara ! Damn !
Kasahara !
- Action ! - The key might be in that bag !
C 'mon monster ! Get her !
Get the hell out ! The camera is rolling !
What ?
Huh ? What the hell is this ?
Yep , it 's moving ! One after another ...
Wow ! Cheesy that so cool ! DOP 's changed ?
What 's going on ?
- Y , your cue ... - You hit me !
- Let 's go . - No one hit me before !
He said it 's your damn cue , brat !
You heard , move your ass ! Chop chop !
- You okay ? - Huh ?
- Calm down . - I 'm calm . I 'm dead calm .
Your Mom 's great .
- Never seen before . - Why did she quit ?
She loses herself in her roles .
She ignores her lines .
One time she broke a star 's arm while filming .
Then she stopped acting , more like she had to stop ?
- One hella actor , huh ? - Hmm ...
Will she be okay ?
Nao ...
It 's okay , I know . just in case ..
- Calm down , Nao . - I 'm calm . I 'm dead calm .
No !
Pom !
She 's ignoring the script !
Zombie , stop her !
What ? I don 't get it !
Calm down , Mrs ...
Help !
Action !
Outta my way !
Don 't worry about me , you gotta stop her , please !
I gotcha !
- No ! - It 's okay .
Who the hell are ya ?
Aw ! You 're gonna break my arm ! Stop her ! Stop the camera !
Pom !
You ! Damn ! Jack ass !
Sorry dear .
Take this ! Jack ass ! Take this !
- Isn 't it too long ? - Huh ?
Thank god .
- Go away ! - What ?
Run away from me ' . ' !
Chinatsu !
- Thanks . - What did I do ?
Can 't think of anything anymore .
- Better that way . - Director ,
we need an axe for the last scene .
- Let her pick it up ! - Eh ?
- Doesn 't matter , go ! - Yes !
Pick up an axe outside !
An axe ...
Lucky me .
- No crane . - What ?
It 's broken .
Change the approach .
- Need to push up 4 m . - Why ?
- The blood drawing , the climax . - Huh ?
The spell revived the zombies . It 's on the script !
Hmm ... let 's cut that scene .
- Hold on . - No time .
- 5 minutes left . - And ?
- We must end with that scene . - I say no need .
I say we freakin ' do !
Who , you ?
I 'm sorry .
I lost my temper .
Mr. Higurashi ,
this is a TV show , not art .
Just finish the show . Your ' average ' will do .
I ... understand !
Uh ... no crane shot . We pull out from the foot of the girl ...
then the credits . Yep , let the DOP know , will you ?
Wait !
How many of you are free now ?
Ko ?
Oh , no ...
You as well ?
What 's that ?
- Crane . - Huh ?
Ko ...
please ...
- Stop ! - That 's it !
That face ! You nailed it goddamnit !
Now the climax ! Make it the last bloody take !
Ko ...
please ...
Stop !
Please Ko ! It 's me !
I 'm begging you !
Wake up !
Ko ...
please ...
Stop !
Please !
I love you .
What the hell ? Follow the script !
What the hell ? Let me finish !
- Well done , beautiful tears ! - Huh ?
This is it , the climax !
15 seconds to the end ..
Ten , nine , eight , seven ,
six , five , four , three ,
two , one ...
Okay , cut !
I was worried how things would go
but the show went well without any trouble . Thanks a lot !
We 're gonna get busy , right ?
Drink anyone ?
Let 's do it .
Ready ...
Sta rt !
Takayuki Hamatsu
Mao
Harumi Shuhama
Kazuaki Nagaya
Manabu Hosoi
Hiroshi Ichihara
Shuntaro Yamazaki
Shinichiro Osawa
Yoshiko Takehara
Miki Yoshida
Ayana Goda
Sakina Asamori
Yuzuki Akiyama
Camera : Takeshi Sone Sound : Komoda Kokichi
Special Make-Up : Kazuhide Shimohata Make-Up : Junko Hirabayashi
Assistant Director : Yuya Nakaizumi , Konosuke Yoshida
Music : Nobuhiro Suzuki , Kyle Nagai
Producer : Koji Ichihashi
Based on the play GHOST IN THE BOX by Ryoichi Wada
Production : Enbu Seminar
DCP Post Production Services : Silk Purse Enterprises
Subtitles : Sayaka Rui
Director , writer editor : Shinichiro Ueda
World Sales : Third Window Films